var questions = [
    {
        "question": 'All motor-propelled vessels must be equipped with',
        "a": 'A cotton skier-down flag of yellow or green color.',
        "b": 'Outboard motors and internal fuel tanks.',
        "c": 'An effective muffler or underwater exhaust system.',
        "d": 'Auxiliary lines, sails, thimbles and key.',
        "correctAnswer": 'C',
    },
    {
        "question": 'Which of the four types of approved flares must be used only in daylight?',
        "a": 'The multi-star flare',
        "b": 'The rocket parachute flare',
        "c": 'The hand flare',
        "d": 'The smoke signal',
        "correctAnswer": 'D',
    },
    {
        "question": 'What are most small boats powered by?',
        "a": 'outboard engines',
        "b": 'inboard engines',
        "c": 'inboard/outboard engines',
        "d": 'jet drives',
        "correctAnswer": 'A',
    },
    {
        "question": 'The following symptoms are related to which condition: slow pulse, confusion, drowsiness, lack of coordination?',
        "a": 'Insomnia',
        "b": 'Heat stroke',
        "c": 'Hypothermia',
        "d": 'Carbon monoxide poisoning',
        "correctAnswer": 'C',
    },
    {
        "question": 'Which factors must be taken into account in determining a safe speed?',
        "a": 'Conditions of visibility and traffic density',
        "b": 'The draft in relation to the available depth of water and the manoeuvrability of the vessel',
        "c": 'Conditions of wind, sea and current, and the proximity of navigational hazards',
        "d": 'All of the above',
        "correctAnswer": 'D',
    },
    {
        "question": "What does a boat's capacity plate tell you?",
        "a": 'how much the boat weighs',
        "b": "the boat's top speed",
        "c": 'the maximum persons capacity',
        "d": 'the number of life jackets required',
        "correctAnswer": 'C',
    },
    {
        "question": "What type of fire extinguisher is required on board a boat equipped with an inboard engine?",
        "a": 'A type fire extinguisher',
        "b": "BC type fire extinguisher",
        "c": 'AB type fire extinguisher',
        "d": 'B type fire extinguisher',
        "correctAnswer": 'C',
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following statements is incorrect regarding carbon monoxide (CO) poisoning?",
        "a": 'Carbone monoxide can build up when two vessels are tied to each other.',
        "b": "Carbon monoxide poisoning occurs when you breathe too much carbon monoxide and it begins to replace the oxygen in your blood.",
        "c": 'It is important to run the engine at idle only in well ventilated areas in order to protect yourself and others from carbon monoxide poisoning.',
        "d": 'Symptoms of carbon monoxide poisoning are: hot, red and dry skin, rapid pulse, rapid and shallow breathing.',
        "correctAnswer": 'D',
    },
    {
        "question": "How must the lettering of the registration number on your boat be displayed?",
        "a": 'written in fancy script',
        "b": "almost the same color as your boat",
        "c": 'not less than 3 inches in height',
        "d": 'displayed on the stern',
        "correctAnswer": 'C',
    },
    {
        "question": "What do visual distress signals have in common?",
        "a": 'They never expire',
        "b": "They are approved by your local police",
        "c": 'They should be locked away to keep them safe',
        "d": 'They should only be used in case of an emergency or distress',
        "correctAnswer": 'D',
    },
]